Hi. I'm Daniel Silver Baker.
Hi 我是 Daniel Silver Baker
For the first half of my professional career,
在我职业生涯的前半段
I worked with young people doing arts-based health programming in New York.
我和一些年轻人在纽约从事艺术方面的编程
I've always been really interested in language, poetry.
我一直对语言和诗歌非常感兴趣
I'm a performance poet.
我是一个表演诗人
In the last five years,
在过去五年中
I've extended my language to also include programming.
我扩展了自己的语言也包括了编程语言
So right now, I'm a freelance web developer
所以现在我成为了一名自由的 web 开发者
and engineer based out of Los Angeles, California.
和软件工程师 主要在 Los Angeles California 区域
I became interested in front-end programming actually working with a group
当我在 Brooklyn 和一群年轻人开发数字程序时
of young people on creating a digital program for young people in Brooklyn.
我对前端编程产生了兴趣
As I was making this program with them,
在和他们合作的过程中
I started to realize that it might be something that I was falling in love with myself.
我开始意识到里面可能也有一些我自己非常喜欢的元素
I became one of those self-taught people.
于是我也成为了一名自学者
I really just scoured the Internet,
我开始在网上浏览网页
I inspected different pages,
检测不同的页面
I tore apart the HTML,
查看他们的 HTML
and eventually I went to NYU,
最后我去了纽约大学
where I studied at the Interactive Telecommunications Program.
在那里开始学习互动传播专业
That's where my love of front-end came into being.
那是我对前端产生热爱的时刻
For me, my real interest is in communicating to people.
对于我来说 我喜欢和其他人交流
So front-end web development lets me develop something that you,
所以前端开发也让我可以开发出一些
the audience, can see as opposed to,
对于观众来说和其他编程方式不一样的东西
not to say something bad about other kinds of development,
并不是说其他的开发方式不好
but programming for computers to talk to each other is for me less
只是我发现前端编程比其他相关的计算机编程更令我激动
exciting than when I found front-end programming and I could program for other people.
因为我可以编写一些更贴近其他人的项目
Getting started in front-end developing can feel difficult.
开始做前端开发有时候会有一些困难
So my number one thing I would say is patience.
所以首先我想要说的是耐心一点
I think patience is such an important part of programming.
我认为在编程中耐心是很重要的东西
This might sound a little up in the air,
听起来好像有点浮夸
but really to enjoy it as much as you can.
但是一定要尽可能的享受它
For me my learning has really come from when I can settle in and I
对于我来说 当你真正安静下来 开始面对那些未知的事情
can give in to the not knowing and then I can find discovery in what I'm doing.
你就可以在过程中发现一些新东西
So little wins I think are a big deal.
每一个小的进步都很重要
I tried to set goals for myself.
我会为自己设定目标
Turn this box blue by the end of the hour and then I
在这个小时结束之前 将这个盒子变成蓝色
could work towards that and it feels amazing once you did it.
然后我就可以向着目标努力 这样通常会很有效
It really for me as a practice of learning magic.
对于我来说它就像学习魔法一般
I think there's mistakes all along the paths being a developer.
在成为开发者的过程中 总是会有很多错误发生
So I think the earliest mistakes that people are
我认为最容易犯的错误就是
prone to make have to do with not trusting yourself.
你通常不信任你自己
I think there's an instinct to really copy and paste code at the beginning,
你通常会有直接复制和粘贴代码的自觉
and I really think there's a benefit to instead of doing that,
但是我真的认为比起这样
to really going through the process yourself.
你自己亲手尝试每一步会更有好处
Writing code from scratch can feel really difficult.
从零开始编写代码会比较困难
There's nothing scarier than an empty page,
不管是编写代码还是写诗
whether it's coding or poetry or anything else.
没有什么比一个空白页更无聊了
But I think there's really something to starting with
但是我真的认为你有必要从一个空白页开始
an empty page and creating those elements out from scratch yourself.
亲手创建出一些元素
At some point, you're going to have to learn to do it yourself.
在某些时候 你必须自己动手去做
So I say throw the crutches out as early as you can.
所以 趁早扔掉你手里的拐杖
For more advanced users,
对于一些高级用户
I would say not to become too comfortable in what you know.
我想说不要对于你所知道的感到过于舒适
There's always new ways to do things that are coming out and there's always
总会有新的方式不断出现 也总有办法去发现其他人正在做什么
ways to discover what other people are doing to bring it to the next level.
然后将他们自己带入一个新高度
So for advanced users,
所以对于高级用户来说
I say push outside your comfort zone.
我想说走出你的舒适区
For beginning users, I say push outside your comfort zone.
对于新手用户来说 也是走出你的舒适区
HTML and CSS or what we think of as building block languages.
HTML 和 CSS 是一些基本的构建语言
So in some ways there are a lot more simple than say JavaScript,
所以它们大多数情况下比 Javascript 要简单很多
which goes well with them or slightly in another world,
JavaScript 和它们结合得很好 但是却像是另一个新世界
but Python is another advanced programming language.
而 Python 又是另外一门高级编程语言
HTML and CSS though,
虽然我们称 HTML 和
well, we call them basic or easy.
CSS 是简单的基础语言
If you're starting from nothing,
但如果你从来没有开始过
if you've never coded before,
从来没有进行过编程
HTML and CSS provide plenty of challenge.
你也会觉得有一定挑战性
Those are about what we create.
这和我们做了什么有关
The other programming languages like JavaScript then
其他的一些编程语言比如 JavaScript
allow us to put those things into interaction with each other,
允许我们和它们互动起来
which can be more complex because it can include equations and math,
但是也会更加复杂 因为它可能会和方程式和数学有关
about the rates of change, and stuff.
变化率等等
But really, it's still programming.
但是不管怎样 它也只是编程
So while I think the hardest thing to do would be going from nothing to say JavaScript,
所以我认为最难的事情是从完全未知走向 JavaScript
by breaking it up, I think it's a good path.
通过把它分解成一小块一小块可能是一个不错的路径
You go from knowing what you know to learning
从刚开始学习知识
the more fundamental languages of HTML and CSS.
到了解 HTML 和 CSS 语言
Then I think you'll feel ready for the jump to something like JavaScript.
我认为你已经准备好了面对新的事物了 比如 JavaScript
I know for myself, once I've created,
我了解这一点 当你创造了
say a blue circle,
一个蓝色圆圈时
I want to see my blue circle move,
你可能会想要它动起来
and that's where something like JavaScript comes in.
这就是 JavaScript 大展身手的地方了